{"Topic": "World Cup Football (updated)", "Subject": "General Knowledge", "Data": [{"Question": "How many teams have won the World Cup since its inception in 1930?", "op1": "8", "op2": "7", "op3": "5", "op4": "4", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Brazil has the most number of World Cup titles to its credit. How many times has it won the World Cup so far?", "op1": "5", "op2": "4", "op3": "6", "op4": "7", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "In which year was the football World Cup held for the first time?", "op1": "1928", "op2": "1930", "op3": "1924", "op4": "1932", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Which country won the first football World Cup?", "op1": "Brazil", "op2": "Germany", "op3": "Uruguay", "op4": "Argentina", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Paul, a marine creature, which supposedly predicted the outcome of many matches in World Cup 2010 was a/an", "op1": "Jelly fish", "op2": "Walrus", "op3": "Octopus", "op4": "Seal", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "In which country is FIFA World Cup 2018 scheduled to be played?", "op1": "Qatar", "op2": "Russia", "op3": "South Korea", "op4": "France", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "To which country does the famous player Ronaldo, who held the record for most number of World Cup goals, belong?", "op1": "France", "op2": "Spain", "op3": "Portugal", "op4": "Brazil", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "In which country are the headquarters of FIFA (International Federation of Association Football) located?", "op1": "Switzerland", "op2": "Brazil", "op3": "France", "op4": "The Netherlands", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Who has the record for scoring the most goals in World Cup history?", "op1": "Ronaldo", "op2": "Diego Maradona", "op3": "Miroslav Klose", "op4": "Lionel Messi", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Who of the following won the World Cup both as the captain and manager of his country's team?", "op1": "Diego Maradona", "op2": "Mario Zagallo", "op3": "Franz Beckenbauer", "op4": "Jupp Derwall", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Which trophy was awarded to the winners of World Cup tournament until 1970?", "op1": "Arsenal Trophy", "op2": "Heisman Trophy", "op3": "Grondona Cup", "op4": "Jules Rimet Trophy", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "What kind of animal was Zabivaka, the mascot for FIFA World Cup 2018?", "op1": "Tiger", "op2": "Cat", "op3": "Polar Bear", "op4": "Wolf", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Who of the following was awarded the Golden Ball or the Best Player Award at the 2018 FIFA World Cup?", "op1": "Luka Modric", "op2": "Harry Kane", "op3": "Romelu Lukaku", "op4": "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "In which year did France win the World Cup earlier?", "op1": "1994", "op2": "1998", "op3": "2002", "op4": "2004", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Thibaut Courtois who was awarded the Golden Glove award for the best goalkeeper at the World Cup 2018 is from which country?", "op1": "Croatia", "op2": "France", "op3": "England", "op4": "Belgium", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Who was the captain of the 2018 World Cup winning team of France?", "op1": "Hugo Lloris", "op2": "Paul Pogba", "op3": "Kylian Mbappe", "op4": "Antoinne Griezmann", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "From which confederation did the most number of teams qualify for the World Cup 2018 final 32?", "op1": "CONCACAF", "op2": "CONMEBOL", "op3": "UEFA", "op4": "CAF", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Who of the following players scored a hat-trick of goals in the World Cup 2018?", "op1": "Cristiano Ronaldo", "op2": "Harry Kane", "op3": "Both (a) and (b)", "op4": "None of the above", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Luzhniki Stadium which hosted the opening and closing ceremonies in World Cup 2018 is located in which city?", "op1": "Moscow", "op2": "Volgograd", "op3": "Saint Petersburg", "op4": "Sochi", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which team was awarded the FIFA Fair Play Award at the World Cup 2018 tournament?", "op1": "England", "op2": "Japan", "op3": "Spain", "op4": "Croatia", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Which of the following was the official song of the FIFA World Cup 2018?", "op1": "All In One Rhythm", "op2": "Live it up", "op3": "Go for it", "op4": "Football in space", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "What name has been given to the special font typeface designed by Brandia Central for writing the official logo Russia 2018 of FIFA World Cup 2018?", "op1": "Kremlin", "op2": "Molot", "op3": "Troika", "op4": "Dusha", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "What name was given to the football used for the final match between France and Croatia at the FIFA World Cup 2018?", "op1": "Telstar Elast", "op2": "Telstar Durlast", "op3": "Telstar Mechta", "op4": "Telstar Plast", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Who of the following was the manager of the French team at the FIFA World Cup 2018 as well as the captain of the team which won the World Cup in 1998?", "op1": "Ricardo Gareca", "op2": "Didier Deschamps", "op3": "Fernando Hierro", "op4": "Juan Carlo Osorio", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Who was selected for the Man of the Match Award in the finals of World Cup 2018?", "op1": "Antoine Griezman", "op2": "Kylian Mbappe", "op3": "Paul Pogba", "op4": "Raphael Varane", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "How much was the prize money awarded to the World Cup winning team France at the tournament?", "op1": "22 million dollars", "op2": "26 million dollars", "op3": "32 million dollars", "op4": "38 million dollars", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Who of the following became the second teenager in the history of World Cup football to score a goal in the finals?", "op1": "Antoine Griezman", "op2": "Kylian Mbappe", "op3": "Paul Pogba", "op4": "Raphael Varane", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "What kind of animal was Fuleco, the mascot for FIFA World Cup 2014?", "op1": "Giant Anteater", "op2": "Alpaca", "op3": "Armadillo", "op4": "Otter", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Who of the following was awarded the Golden Ball or the Best Player Award at the 2014 FIFA World Cup?", "op1": "Paul Pogba", "op2": "Lionel Messi", "op3": "Neymar", "op4": "Mario Gotze", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Who of the following was awarded the Golden Boot Award for most goals in the tournament of 2014?", "op1": "Miroslave Klose", "op2": "James Rodriguez", "op3": "Thomas Muller", "op4": "Neymar", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Who was awarded the Golden Glove award for the best goalkeeper at the World Cup 2014?", "op1": "Manuel Neuer", "op2": "Tim Krul", "op3": "Julio Cesar", "op4": "Sergio Romero", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Who scored the winning goal for Germany against Argentina in the finals of World Cup 2014?", "op1": "Mario Gotze", "op2": "Miroslave Klose", "op3": "Mats Hummels", "op4": "Thomas Muller", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "How many countries played at the World Cup 2014 tournament?", "op1": "36", "op2": "32", "op3": "28", "op4": "30", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Match the players (winners of individual awards) with their countries?", "op1": "A - 3; B - 4; C - 1; D - 2", "op2": "A - 2; B - 1; C - 4; D - 3", "op3": "A - 2; B - 4; C - 1; D - 3", "op4": "A - 2; B - 3; C - 1; D - 4", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Who was the captain of the 2014 World Cup winning team from Germany?", "op1": "Philipp Lahm", "op2": "Manuel Neuer", "op3": "Miroslave Klose", "op4": "Mats Hummels", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "How many teams from the Asian continent participated in the FIFA World Cup 2014 tournament?", "op1": "Four", "op2": "Two", "op3": "One", "op4": "Three", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Who of the following players scored a hat-trick of goals in the World Cup 2014?", "op1": "Thomas Muller", "op2": "Xherdan Shaqiri", "op3": "Both (a) and (b)", "op4": "None of the above", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "At which of the following stadiums was the final match between Germany and Argentina played in World Cup 2014?", "op1": "Mineirao", "op2": "Maracana", "op3": "Arena Castelao", "op4": "Arena Da Amazonia", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which team was awarded the FIFA Fair Play Award at the World Cup 2014 tournament?", "op1": "Germany", "op2": "Netherlands", "op3": "Spain", "op4": "Columbia", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "What was the slogan of the FIFA World Cup 2014?", "op1": "All In One Rhythm", "op2": "Celebrate Humanity", "op3": "Football For Peace", "op4": "A Time To Make Friends", "Answer": 1}]}